## JUDITH TUYISINGIZE

tuvisingize4@gmail.com | +1 585.478.2030 | LinkedIn Profile

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a highly-skilled, communicative problem solver with the ability to adapt well in any environment. My goal is to work at a fast-growing company where I can apply my knowledge of coding languages specializing in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MERN stack and data structures.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in International Business (Minor in Accounting) | Rochester Institute of Technology Associate of Science in Liberal Arts | Community College of Vermont Software Development Certificate | Burlington Code Academy

2020 2016 Exp. June 2023

#### **SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

Python	FCPX	JavaScript	HTML	CSS
Git/Github	MongoDB	Express	React	Node.js
Agile/Scrum	API's	Client Relations	Data Analysis	Project Management

### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

Blackjack Game | Python

- Allows human users to play Blackjack against a computer opponent and provides custom solution proposals using Python
- Used general terms including append, pop, random module

Fashion Blog | JavaScript, HTML, CSS

- Designed a front-end website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for a fashion designer
- Communicated with a client and Informed design decisions about color and different text styles

Focused on direct observation of multiple patients who are harming themselves and others.

## Jeopardy I JavaScript, HTML, CSS

A front end modeled through the famous host show where the build consists of a mobile-first responsive application through the use of JavaScript, HTML, and CSS and utilized industry-leading Flexbox and Grid modules to complete the project

The Guess The Number Game | JavaScript

Terminal-based game utilizing JavaScript fundamentals (conditionals, loops, and functions) as well as the use of Node's stdin and stdout streams and utilized built-in library, readline

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **UVM Medical Center | Burlington, VT**

- Clinical Patient Safety Attendant
  - Responsible for working closely with fellow nursing teams to care for and observe patients, document the statuses of patients every hour, and provide reports to transitioning teams.

## **Environmental Service Worker II**

August 2021 - February 2023

February 2023 - Present

- Performed variety of housekeeping duties, conducted specialized cleaning, and was responsible for environmental services of
- Worked within a team to ensure all duties were completed each shift and communicated with supervisors, hospital staff, patients, and visitors to ensure and clean environment that was upheld to the highest standards

# Rochester Regional Health | Rochester, NY

Food Service Associate

May 2019 - January 2021

- Provided exceptional food service to patients, staff, and visitors, ensuring a positive dining experience.
- Maintained a clean and sanitary work environment, following health and safety regulations.
- Collaborated with a diverse team to meet service goals and deliver high-quality meals on time.